drippler.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Drippler

**Drippler Privacy Policy**

**Version 4.0**

**Last Revised: June 29, 2018**

At Drippler, we take protecting your privacy seriously. In order for our sites, and services (collectively “Services”) to function properly, we need to collect and use some of your personal information (defined below). We want you to understand what personal information we collect and how it is used.

This policy is incorporated as part of the Terms of Service that apply to your use of the Services. When you use our Services, you acknowledge that you have accepted the Terms of Service and this policy without exception. You also acknowledge that you consent to our privacy practices, including our use, transfer, and disclosure of your personal information.

If you do not consent to the Terms of Service or this policy, please do not use our Services or provide any personal information.

**What’s covered by this policy**

Any Drippler-affiliated site, product or service which links to this policy and any collection, storage, transfer, sharing, disclosure and handling of your personal information when you use our Services which we define below.

This policy does not cover and we are not responsible for third-party sites or applications that may be linked from our sites; linking to them does not imply an endorsement. We are not responsible for these sites or applications or any information they may collect. You should always review the privacy policy of any third-party site or application.

**Personal information we collect**

When you download and use the Services, we may collect the personal information detailed below.

Personal information is information that that specifically identifies you (like your name and email address) including any (i) behavioral information that may be derived from your use of the Services or (ii) information that might otherwise be collected when you use certain features of your phone in connection with the application that may contain, among other things:

  * Your name (if you provided this upon registration for the Services)
  * Your email address (if you provided this upon registration for the Services)
  * The location from where you have accessed the Services
  * The mobile device identifier provided by your mobile device operating system
  * Your answers to company questions and preference surveys
  * Statistics regarding your use of the Services
  * The frequency of your use of the Services
  * Ads (as defined below) and other sponsored content in the application that you have clicked on
  * Third-party content accessed via the Services
  * The content of your queries and chat logs in the application
  * Other applications you have installed or uninstalled on your device
  * Your IP Address

In addition, if you choose to register for any Services and/or access any services in connection with an external social network (such as Facebook, Google+ or Twitter) (each an “External Network”) we may also collect certain additional elements of personal information, in accordance with the permissions that you grant us the first time that you registered for/accessed Services using your External Network profile which may include any of the following:

  * Your user ID/personal identifier on the External Network
  * Gender
  * Age
  * Items that you have “liked” on an External Network
  * Your “Friends” in the External Network
  * Information based on your use of the application
  * Items and actions that you allow to be published on an External Network (such as, the “Like a Drip” and “Share a Drip” functionalities)
  * Advertisements and other sponsored content in the application that you have clicked on
  * Services you subscribe for including any Premium Services and any cancellation of any such subscription

**Information we collect when you visit our websites**

Drippler and its partners use cookies or similar technologies on our websites to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

Drippler also gathers certain information about the use of Drippler’s services, including the number of unique visitors, the frequency of visits, how users interact with the sites, user experience preferences, IP address, and other information that may help Drippler improve the user experience, mitigate fraudulent activity, and comply with legal requirements. Such information may include, but is not limited to the following:

Log information

When you visit Drippler’s sites we automatically collect and store certain information in our server logs. This type of information includes details of how you interacted with our services. It may include personal information such as: IP address, Unique Device Identifier, the content of web pages, transactions with APIs (Application Program Interface), activity and content of visitor interaction with call center representatives; application usage activity, hardware information, hardware and system settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, referral URL, etc.

Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is managed by your web browser or other application and stored on your local system. Drippler uses session and persistent cookies to, among other things, identify your computer during a particular interaction and analyze your behavior during a particular visit. Most web browsers provide you with the ability to accept or decline cookies, as well as to be warned each time a cookie is being sent. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully use Drippler’s services.

Pixel tags

Pixel tags, also known as web beacons, help Drippler better manage user experience and content tracking. Pixel tags are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, which provide a similar function to cookies and are used to track user interaction with content provided by Drippler or an affiliate organization. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, pixel tags are embedded invisibly within content. The small size and transparency of pixel tags are not intended to deceive content recipients, but minimize distraction.

**How we use your personal information**

We are committed to protecting your privacy and earning your trust.  It is our intent to give you as much control as reasonably practicable over the privacy and use of your personal information. The personal information we collect is used mainly to:

  * Fulfill the Service to you
  * Complete your purchase
  * Establish and verify your identity
  * Activate and maintain your account
  * Handle and resolve billing disputes
  * Monitor and maintain the performance and functionality of the device consistent with your choices
  * Provide technical support and click-to-chat functionality
  * Protect and improve our Services
  * Offer updates, notices and other information about applications and Services available from Drippler or its affiliates as permitted by law. (Note: at any time you may choose to withdraw your consent to Drippler’s use or disclosure of your Information for marketing and promotional purposes by contacting Drippler’s as outlined in Where to turn with questions section of this policy)
  * Respond to your questions, inquiries, comments and instructions
  * To enforce the applicable Terms of Service
  * Comply with the law and defend our rights
  * Track and analyze de-identified data and provide such data to third parties that provide services to Drippler
  * Protect against fraud and potential fraud
  * Notify you of any known breach of your personal information
  * Maintain the security and integrity of the application, and Drippler’s systems and Services.

**Sharing personal information with third parties by Drippler**

Other than as expressly described elsewhere in this policy, we will not share your personal information with any third-party, except in the following cases (and then, only to the extent reasonably necessary under the circumstances): (a) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this policy or the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations of it; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to your support requests; (e) to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Drippler, its users and the general public; (g) when Drippler is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Drippler; or (h) pursuant to your explicit approval, in order to supply certain services you have requested from Drippler.

**Advertising**

From time to time, we may allow third-party advertisers (“ **Advertisers** ”) to sponsor advertising content or links (“ **Ads** ”) that can be directly accessed from within the Services.   In order to provide Ads that we think would be of most interest to our users, we may share certain Information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) to Advertisers. For example, we might provide an analysis of data that says “1000 users in California who accessed the application in the month of June using a Samsung Galaxy S7 shared a Drip on Facebook about free off-line map applications for Android.”  That said, keep in mind that if you click through links to leave the application and go to the Advertisers’ sites, those sites may gather information about you.  This policy does not cover the practices of any Advertiser or any other third-party.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these third-parties, check out the [NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). For information about Facebook Native Ads click [here](https://m.facebook.com/ads/ad_choices).

**How we protect your Information**

We use commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical controls best practices to protect your personal information including data encryption where appropriate; however, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure the security of personal information during its transmission between you and us. Accordingly, you acknowledge that when you transmit such personal information, you do so at your own risk. We will notify you of any confirmed security breach of your personal information to the extent required by and in accordance with state and federal law.

**How you are notified if the policy changes**

We may change this policy from time to time. If we do, we will post the updated policy with the last revised date. Your continued use of the application means that you consent to the updates. You should periodically read the policy to understand our privacy practices.

If we make material changes to this policy, then we will notify you in the application or by email and seek your affirmative consent.

**Communicating with you electronically**

By downloading and using our application, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically. This includes any required notifications (i.e. legal, technical, regulatory, security, privacy) relating to your use of the application.

**Commercial messages**

Where required, Drippler will seek your express consent to send such messages. This consent is sought by Drippler Ltd., 648 Grassmere Park, Nashville, TN 37211. You may withdraw your consent by using the "unsubscribe" link located at the bottom of our messages, contacting us at the address listed above, or by emailing [privacy@drippler.com](mailto:privacy@drippler.com?subject=Privacy%20inquiry%20from%20drippler.com).  

**How long we keep your information**

Drippler will retain your personal information as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy, unless a longer retention period is required or not prohibited by applicable law.

**Your rights related to your personal information**

While we take various steps to ensure the accuracy and completeness of your personal information, we rely upon you to provide accurate and complete information when interacting with us.

Upon your request and as allowed or required by law and consistent with our applicable partner agreements, you may request Drippler to take the following actions with your personal information: (i) provide you with a copy, (ii) correct, (iii) update, or (iv) delete your personal information. To make such a request, or if you have a privacy-related complaint, please contact Drippler via postal mail or email as provided in the Where to turn with questions section of this policy. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. ](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.%C2%A0)  

**Mobile analytics**

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our application on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.

**A few notes about social media**

Please be aware that any personal information that you submit to a social media site such as Facebook, Instagram or Twitter is done at your own risk and without any expectation of privacy. Drippler cannot control the actions of social media site users and is not responsible for any content or submissions contained on such sites. You should always review the privacy policy of any third-party website or application.

By using any functionality that permits submissions to social media sites, you are indicating that you have reviewed the applicable privacy policy and terms of use of that site. Additionally, in the event that we offer functionality through the application that permits the posting of content on social media, please be aware that these sites may allow you to publicly post, and share this content. Drippler cannot guarantee the privacy and safety of these sites and is therefore not responsible for any content you post. Use these features at your own risk.

**Children under 13**

The application is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that your child is accessing the application and providing personal information without your consent, please contact us by using the information provided below. We will take steps to remove personal information from our storage systems and terminate the account if we determine that a child under 13 has accessed the application.

**Your California privacy rights**

Under California law, users who are residents of California are permitted to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year (if any) and the names and addresses of those third parties.  Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge.  As of the date of the Last Update to this policy (written above), we currently do not share any personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Consent to processing and transfer of information**

We may transfer personal information that we collect about you outside of the country in which it was collected.  If you are visiting regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring personal information about yourself, to a country and jurisdiction that may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which it was collected. By doing so, you are consenting to the transfer of personal information about yourself to the U.S. you are also consenting to the use and disclosure of personal information about yourself, as described in this policy.

Important Note: this service is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Drippler has taken steps to prevent EEA users from accessing the application.

**Accountability and governance**

Drippler has implemented various measures to monitor compliance with and enforce this policy.

**Where to turn with questions**

If you have any questions about this policy, about our application, or want to request access to, correction, or deletion of your personal information, or a privacy-related complaint, you can contact Drippler by email at [privacy@drippler.com](mailto:privacy@drippler.com?subject=Privacy%20inquiry%20from%20drippler.com)

You may also contact us at:

Drippler

Attn: Privacy Office

c/o Office of the General Counsel

648 Grassmere Park

Nashville, TN 37211  

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.
